<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
 <string name="help_main_text">
 <![CDATA[
<p>
<b>
Main Help
</b>
</p>
<p>
Tap an icon below for specific help on that topic. Use the device\'s back button to return to main screen.
</p>
 ]]>
</string>

 <string name="help_edit_icon">Edit</string>

 <string name="help_edit_title">Editing</string>

<string name="help_edit">
 <![CDATA[
<p>
<b>
Reminder Editing
</b>
</p>
<p>
<u>Editing</u><br>
To edit a reminder, first expand the reminder you would like to edit by tapping on the name to show the item\'s details. Then
tap on the pencil icon on the left hand side of the details. This will take you to the reminder editor.
The name and details will be filled in for the reminder selected.
</p>
<p>
<u>Saving</u><br>
Make any changes you would like to the details and then use
the device\'s back button to return to the main screen. All updates will be saved upon leaving the editor.
</p>
 ]]>
 </string>

 <string name="help_create_icon">Create</string>

 <string name="help_create_title">Creating</string>

<string name="help_create">
 <![CDATA[
<p>
<b>
Reminder Creation
</b>
</p>
<p>
<u>Creating</u><br>
To create a new reminder, tap the plus icon on the action bar of the main screen that is located between the app title,
Open Reminder, and the help symbol. Tapping on the icon will take you to the reminder editor. There,
you will be able to type in a name for the reminder, select the mode of operation (time of day or timer),
select the time or timer interval, and select the days you would like to repeat the reminder on.
</p>
<p>
<u>Timer Mode</u><br>
If timer is selected as the mode of operation, a time range selector is revealed at the bottom of the editor
to allow the timer to operate
between certain hours of the day, such as 9:00am to 5:00pm for example.
</p>
<p>
<u>Time of Day Mode</u><br>
If time of day is selected as the mode of operation, selecting the time using the number selector will
show the hours in military format, from 0 to 24. Therefor, if you would like to set the time for 5:00pm
you would need to select 17 as the hour.
</p>
<p>
<u>Naming</u><br>
The name of the reminder needs to be filled in for the reminder to save. Blank reminders
will be discarded upon leaving the editor.
</p>
 ]]>
 </string>

 <string name="help_general_icon">General</string>

 <string name="help_general_title">General Help</string>

<string name="help_general">
 <![CDATA[
<p>
<b>
General Help
</b>
</p>
 <p>
Open Reminder is a simple app that allows you to create repeating notifications for specific times and days
or time intervals. The main screen contains a list of the reminders you have created.
</p>
 <p>
 <u>Navigating</u><br>
Navigation in Open Reminder is accomplished by selecting a button, such as create or help, to
 go to a new screen. The device\'s back button is then used to return to the main screen.
</p>
<p>
<u>Open/Close Reminders</u><br>
Tapping on the name
of a reminder will expand the item and show details about the times and dates selected. This also reveals controls
that allow you to start/stop the reminder, edit it, and delete it. Tapping on the name of the
reminder again will collapse the detail view.
</p>
<p>
<u>Countdown Timer</u><br>
If a reminder is running, the time displayed to the right of the name will show the time remaining
until a notification for the reminder is sounded, plus the time will be counting down. If the reminder is
stopped, the time will either show the actual time a reminder is set for or the timer interval.
</p>
 ]]>
 </string>

 <string name="help_start_icon">Start</string>

 <string name="help_start_title">Starting/Stopping</string>

<string name="help_start">
 <![CDATA[
 <p>
 <b>
Reminder Starting/Stopping
 </b>
 </p>
<p>
<u>Starting/Stopping</u><br>
To start or stop a reminder, first tap on the name of the reminder to expand the item\'s details. The
start or stop button will be on the right hand side of the details, just under the reminder\'s
countdown timer. If the reminder is already started, the icon displayed will be a stop button. If the
reminder is already stopped, the icon displayed will be a start (or play) button. Tapping on the icon
will alternate between the reminder starting and stopping.
</p>
<p>
<u>Mode of Operation</u><br>
If the mode of operation is set to timer, stopping and then restarting a reminder will reset the timer
interval. If the mode is set to time of day, restarting the reminder will continue the countdown to the
specified time.
</p>
 ]]>
 </string>

 <string name="help_delete_icon">Remove</string>

 <string name="help_delete_title">Removing</string>

<string name="help_delete">
 <![CDATA[
 <p>
<b>
Reminder Removal
</b>
 </p>
<p>
<u>Deleting</u><br>
To remove a reminder from the list, first tap the name of the reminder to expand it\'s details if it is
not already open. The delete icon will be on the right hand side of the reminder\'s details just under
the start/stop button. Tapping on the delete icon will bring up a confirmation dialog asking if you are
certain you would like to remove the selected reminder. Choosing yes will remove the reminder from the list.
</p>
 ]]>
 </string>

<string name="help_error">
    <p>No help available for selected topic.</p>
</string>

</resources>